Reporting live from Hypers Club in
Atlanta for Comedy Hype News, I'm
Symphony. Well, Amanda Seals is no
stranger to controversy, and it appears
she's rubbed people the wrong way once
again. After questioning the support
former President Barack Obama receives
amongst black people, even asking her
viewers to tell her what did Obama do
specifically for black people. Seals
made these comments on her podcast and
the Shade Room would share a clip of the
Bowment on their own Instagram page. She
would go on to tell a story seeing Quest
Love post about Obama on social media
with him saying he's noticed many people
nitpicking at the former president. This
would cause Seals to try and unfollow
Quest Love. However, when attempting to
do so, she realized Quest Love had
already unfollowed her. She would go on
to express her confusion on why so many
people hold Obama in such a high regard.
I see lots of folks
really still loving Obama
and I be like
still
and even if like
you have an affinity towards Obama when
I see people and when I say people I'm
talking about Quest Love. I saw Quest
Love post something about Obama and he
was like, "You know, I've been seeing a
lot of folks nitpicking
Obama lately."
And then I went to unfollow him, but he
had already unfollowed me.
So, I don't know how at this point in
this time people are still calling, you
know, like a friend of mine still like,
"But Obama and Michelle are my forever
floatus." And I'm like, "Why?" saying
things like Obama did he did more
specifically for us. Please tell me what
did Obama do specifically for black
people? Please
tell me
please.
Obama was a great orator orator. He
inspired many people with his presence,
but that does not avail him of critique
and talking about his bad choices and
policies. Inspired them to do what? What
did inspire? What did Obama inspire them
to do with his presence? Aspire to be a
part of establishments.
He never spoke about reparations. He
never spoke about police protections,
about securing police protections for
black people or just for anyone,
honestly. Just like qualified immunity
should be removed in general.
He said we couldn't have Medicare for
all because the insurance companies
provide jobs.
Like what do we you know like at some
point your politics has to come beyond
identity and that is what so many of us
are stuck in the identity politics which
literally is just oh cuz they look like
me. Representation is not
a generic concept.
So, should we be proud that Clarence
Thomas is on the Supreme Court?
Should we? Seals wouldn't stop there,
but would go on to criticize Obama,
referring to some of his policies as bad
choices. She hears many people saying
Obama inspired them. And she would ask,
"Inspired them to do what?" Seals would
condemn Obama for never speaking about
reparations, qualified immunity, police
protections for black people, or anyone.
Now, it seems like many would find issue
with Seal's comments as several social
media users would respond and object to
what she had to say, including Jamie
Fox. Fox would jump into the Shay room's
comments writing, "Barack Obama will
forever be my hero. 400 years of slavery
and for him to emerge victorious. It's
more than policy. It's legacy." Darnell
Rawlings was another notable figure to
respond to Seals asking, "What does this
topic do for black people? At this
point, podcasters sit back and ask,
"What can I say that will help my
engagement?"
One social media user would disapprove
of Seals critiquing Obama when Trump is
currently in office doing more harm than
good. They wrote, "Imagine making Obama
the villain when there's a whole a white
nationalist sitting in the Oval Office
whose party wants to strip millions of
Americans from Obamacare and 10 million
from Medicaid, which Obama also
expanded."
While another social media user would
take the time to answer Seal's question
by mentioning several bills passed under
Obama's watch. They wrote the Affordable
Care Act, the Fair Sentencing Act, the
Earned Income Tax Credit, Child, the
Small Business Administration, the
Consumer Financial Protection Bureau,
the Home Affordable Modification
Program, just to name a few.
Now, Obama not doing much for the black
community while he was in office has
been a talking point for quite some
time. So, Sills isn't alone when it
comes to this narrative. Still, the
backlash she received would cause her to
respond via Instagram live. Even
mentioning her past request for the Sha
Room to not post her. defending her own
comments. She would say folks who still
believe in the sanctity of the
presidential office,
which I do not.
I also, you know, saw how the Shade Room
does what they do, which in their effort
to be a tool of weaponization against
black people, uh, cut and edited up my
words, because they can't show a video
of what I'm actually saying. They always
have to chop and screw it.
They always have to chop and screw it.
And it's like, if you're not going to
actually show what I actually said, then
why are you posting it? By the way, I
have told them, I have asked them
several times, do not post me. Do not
use me
as a tool
of pushing your pedig pedigogy. Do not.
and they continue to do so, which in my
opinion is an indicator of their
continued effort to be a divisive force.
So, what do you guys think about Amanda
Seals wondering why Obama still receives
support from the black community despite
not doing much for black people? Do you
agree? Why or why not? Let us know in
the comments below. And stay up to date
with the latest news and comedy by
subscribing right here to our YouTube
channel. Hit the bell and select all so
you can receive notifications to all of
our content and not just some. Check out
Hypers Club for all your cool and
original merchandise and content. And
for our YouTube viewers, if you
appreciated this update, don't forget
you can send us a super thanks by
hitting the button below and you can tip
us what you want to show your support.
Reporting live from Hypers Club in
Atlanta for Comedy Hype News, I'm
Symphony